<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[brennx0rblog.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The brennx0r.com blog.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 21:13:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Planning Our Recent 2019 UK Trip! 🚀 💂‍♀️]]></title><description><![CDATA[As you may have seen from recent tweets, Jer and I recently took a trip to the UK. Specifically, London, then Scotland, then back to London…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//2019_uk_trip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//2019_uk_trip/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;As you may have seen from recent tweets, Jer and I recently took a trip to the UK. Specifically, London, then Scotland, then back to London. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea for the trip was kicked off when reflecting upon going to Maui for my birthday last year. It was an incredible experience, and I wanted to be able to reciprocate for Jer by taking him to the top locations on his “bucket list”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Various folks on Twitter have requested that I create a blog post which discusses the process I use to plan a trip. I hope you find the below information useful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;So now that there’s a location in mind, how the heck to begin planning? 🤔&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;🗣 Collaboration Tools Make It Happen!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are planning a trip with anyone, you’re gonna need a collaboration tool which you can collectively reference what needs to be planned, what’s already been considered and booked, as well as a common reference place for information - hotel names and addresses, booking reference numbers, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These tools can look anything like the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keybase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Drive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git(hu|la)b&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these can be fine choices, but the important bit is that everyone involved in the planning should enjoy using the tool, and the tool should have some security-mindedness (ACLs, etc.) so that if you opt to include sensitive information, this information is kept safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below I’ll go through the detail concerning all the bits and bobs I find to be handy in this common collaboration space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;📅 Timeline of Events&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Jer and me, doing touristy stuff doesn’t rank highly on the list (if at all), so we don’t need to manage every hour of the day with markers of all those little events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, it still makes sense when planning a trip (especially one with multiple locations involved) to have a timeline of events within easy reach. Even if you think you are planning a “simple trip”, having a timeline will help tease all sorts of shapes/sizes of logistics to you haven’t immediately considered concerning the timings between the transportation, flights, hotel, meals. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, you may realize that by booking an early morning flight that you have consequently cheated yourself out of a decent breakfast at the hotel and will consequently either need to seek out food at the airport, or schedule a later flight. Or, you may find that by arriving late in the evening, unless you call the hotel and schedule a late-checkin ahead of time, no one will be available to give you a room key. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going through this exercise will take a bit of time up-front, this will ultimately &lt;em&gt;save&lt;/em&gt; you time, anxiety, and headache of having to deal with the fallout of a poorly considered timing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#timeline&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  In our recent trip, Jer used emoji markers with a legend for various things and it was &lt;strong&gt;DELIGHTFUL&lt;/strong&gt;. 💜&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1UEENlY462nlyEfyC-sGdklDfSEOFOfqFC5q_itmI-_4&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Drive Spreadsheet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared Calendars&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://support.apple.com/kb/ph2690?locale=en_US&quot;&gt;Apple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://support.google.com/calendar/answer/37082?hl=en&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;📋 To-Do List&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seems obvious, but mentioning here regardless! I live by to-do lists. In a collaborative setting, doubly so because it makes sure that everyone is on the same page at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, in seeing and making use of the list, it may prompt the brain to think of other things which should be added to the list. For example, in the last trip after ‘completing’ the To-Do list, I noticed that we hadn’t considered taxi from a train station to a very remote hotel in the evening. 😅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#bookingsreservations-status&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;🗝📕 ‘What’s Booked’ Metadata&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can be flight, car, train, hotel, and all sorts of other reference information. A few pointers before adding the information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you really need the sensitive information in the collaboration tool?&lt;/strong&gt; Some providers don’t really need this information anymore, and you can communicate with them directly via mobile apps instead of having to keep track of reference or booking numbers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure that the collaboration tool is secure&lt;/strong&gt;, where only contributors involved in the trip can reference the information. Do your research to see if the tool is secure enough for your purposes. Not sure? Don’t store your information in the tool. ✨&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#flight-information&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;💡 Open Dreams / Questions / Logistics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daydreaming about the possibilities during a trip is lovely, so why not share those thoughts so that the ideas aren’t lost? I’ve found that even when we find we don’t have time on &lt;em&gt;this trip&lt;/em&gt; for a dream, that we can save that idea for a later voyage. Sharing dreams brings joy. 🌈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#-ideas--wouldnt-it-be-neat-if&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;🌯 In Conclusion…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that these templates, pointers, and examples helped to spark new ideas about your upcoming adventures. If there’s a section which you’d like more information, or if you’d like to engage with me on related topics, please feel free to DM me on Twitter (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/brennx0r&quot;&gt;@brennx0r&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers! &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bullet-Journaling]]></title><description><![CDATA[A couple months ago I purchased a Cricut Explore Air 2 following the binge watch of YouTube videos showcasing comparisons between various…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//bullet-journaling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//bullet-journaling/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A couple months ago I purchased a Cricut Explore Air 2 following the binge watch of YouTube videos showcasing comparisons between various models. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ch23OY8z5Fo&quot;&gt;This video&lt;/a&gt; was great in doing various tests (cut precision, speed test, sound test) between the machines, which led me to buy the Cricut!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I decided to unbox it and do a couple of basic projects to better understand the features. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Verdict:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; It’s an awesome little machine and I’m looking forward to using it for all sorts of different projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first big project? Bullet Journaling template stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m putting together the scaffold of a YouTube video on the subject of effective bullet journaling, which will lead into a quick how-to on creating templates for quickly putting together a new book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Scaffold&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;- What is/Why Bullet Journaling?
- General Starting Layout
  - Intro 
- Modifying the &amp;#39;Default&amp;#39; Layout
- Bullet Journaling as Agile
- Demo / Process
  - Starting point: Chronological notebook (not using bullet journaling, per say)
  - Iteration: Noticing Patterns, Grouping What&amp;#39;s Important
  - Create the Bullet Journal
    - Draw out the format 
    - Create Template Stickers
    - Move boldly forward&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that y’all enjoy it once it’s posted.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[botd]]></title><description><![CDATA[In a Twitter conversation between a couple friends, the topic of 
“Which Belcher are you?” came up. And clearly, I am Bob. Clearly. This has…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//botd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//botd/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;In a Twitter conversation between a couple friends, the topic of
“Which Belcher are you?” came up. And clearly, I am Bob. Clearly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has led to one of the friends in the conversation - @sweetpavement - to
begin to prompt me for a Burger of the Day (BOTD) each weekday as a tweet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this has been going on for longer than a week, I’m finding that an archive
list is now needed to make sure that I’m not repeating puns, and to showcase
this sacriliciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;BOTD&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When I Dip, You Dip, We Dip! Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Burger with Swiss and onions on a traditional baguette with jus on the side)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/12/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pleased to Meat You Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (3 quarter pound patties - beef, pork, and chorizo - with caramelized onions layered between)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/11/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curry On My Wayward Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Panko-ed patty topped with traditional Japanese curry)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/10/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I Am a Super Fungi Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Filled with buttery chanterelle and lobster mushrooms and a kiss of swiss cheese)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/7/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We Make a Great Pear Burger!&lt;/strong&gt; (Super thin slices of pear, crispy applewood smoked bacon)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/6/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kind of a big dill burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Tzatziki sauce, extra dill, thin sliced tomatoes and cucumbers)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/5/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The I Do Not Want To Taco Bout It Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Seasoned patty w/ additional taco meat on top, sharp cheddar, tomato, lettuce, sour cream, and salty tears)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/3/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nacho ordinary burger!&lt;/strong&gt; (Thin tortilla strips w/ gourmet queso)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11/30/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Make Miso Happy Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Hugged by a lattice of bacon and kissed with micro greens)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11/29/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Goudas around comes around burger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11/28/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Updating website; Woes Ensue!]]></title><description><![CDATA[After not updating my site for a couple of months, I was looking to update with a new blog post. As it turns out, I had forgotten the setup…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//updating-site-woes-ensue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//updating-site-woes-ensue/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;After not updating my site for a couple of months, I was looking to update with a new blog post. As it turns out, I had forgotten the setup/layout for the Gatsby starter I was using, so updating it was very difficult. I ended up scrapping the whole thing for another starter template which is much simpler, easier to read and extend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other woes I ran into had to deal with the npm module &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt;, caching and deployment. In trying to deploy to repo &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;brennx0r.github.io&lt;/code&gt;, master branch - I kept getting this error:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;bash
fatal: A branch named ‘master’ already exists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;npm ERR! code ELIFECYCLE
npm ERR! errno 1
npm ERR! gatsby-starter-blog@1.0.0 deploy: &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gatsby build &amp;amp;&amp;amp; gh-pages -d public -b &amp;gt; master -r git@github.com:brennx0r/brennx0r.github.io.git&lt;/code&gt;
npm ERR! Exit status 1
npm ERR! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After scouring a number of sites (and frustratingly getting the ‘answer’ of referring back to the Gatsby reference material which does not explain how to fix the problem), I was finally able to see some documentation via the &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt; readme about a potential solution which ended up resolving it for me:  Clearing the cache for &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt; via &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;node_modules/gh-pages/.cache&lt;/code&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passing along this information to folks who may also be looking for a fix. 💜 ✨&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/wisdom_of_the_ancients.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;Wisdom of the Ancients&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moving Over to Gatsby]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is the first post since migrating my personal website from using Middleman to using GatsbyJS + Dimension Starter. 🚀 Doing the…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//moving-over-to-gatsby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//moving-over-to-gatsby/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is the first post since migrating my personal website from using Middleman to using GatsbyJS + Dimension Starter. 🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing the migration was a whole lot more straightforward than I thought it would be. What made the ease of migration possible was mainly due to the existance of modules, starters, and excellent documentation to help with getting started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m very excited to begin my journey in working more actively with the JavaScript ecosystem. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having been rooted in the Ruby community for several years, it’s an interesting change of pace to take a peek into what other communities are doing, what the development patterns are, and how folks interact with eachother.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>