<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[brennx0rblog.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The brennx0r.com blog.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 22:45:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Bullet-Journaling]]></title><description><![CDATA[A couple months ago I purchased a Cricut Explore Air 2 following the binge watch of YouTube videos which showcased comparisons between…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//bullet-journaling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//bullet-journaling/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A couple months ago I purchased a Cricut Explore Air 2 following the binge watch of YouTube videos which showcased comparisons between various models. (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ch23OY8z5Fo&quot;&gt;This video&lt;/a&gt; was great in doing various tests (cut precision, speed test, sound test) between the machines, which led me to buy the Cricut.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things have been quite busy until late, and yesterday I was able to unbox and do a couple of basic projects to better understand the features. Verdict: It’s an awesome little machine and I’m looking forward to using it for all sorts of different projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first big project? Bullet Journaling template stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m putting together the scaffold of a YouTube video on the subject of effective bullet journaling, which will lead into a quick how-to on creating templates for quickly putting together a new book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scaffold roughly is this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What is/Why Bullet Journaling?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;General Starting Layout&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intro &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modifying the ‘Default’ Layout&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bullet Journaling as Agile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Demo / Process&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starting point: Chronological notebook (not using bullet journaling, per say)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iteration: Noticing Patterns, Grouping What’s Important&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create the Bullet Journal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draw out the format &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create Template Stickers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move boldly forward&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that y’all enjoy it once it’s posted.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Updating website; Woes Ensue!]]></title><description><![CDATA[After not updating my site for a couple of months, I was looking to update with a new blog post. As it turns out, I had forgotten the setup…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//updating-site-woes-ensue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//updating-site-woes-ensue/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;After not updating my site for a couple of months, I was looking to update with a new blog post. As it turns out, I had forgotten the setup/layout for the Gatsby starter I was using, so updating it was very difficult. I ended up scrapping the whole thing for another starter template which is much simpler, easier to read and extend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other woes I ran into had to deal with the npm module &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt;, caching and deployment. In trying to deploy to repo &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;brennx0r.github.io&lt;/code&gt;, master branch - I kept getting this error:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;bash
fatal: A branch named ‘master’ already exists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;npm ERR! code ELIFECYCLE
npm ERR! errno 1
npm ERR! gatsby-starter-blog@1.0.0 deploy: &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gatsby build &amp;amp;&amp;amp; gh-pages -d public -b &amp;gt; master -r git@github.com:brennx0r/brennx0r.github.io.git&lt;/code&gt;
npm ERR! Exit status 1
npm ERR! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After scouring a number of sites (and frustratingly getting the ‘answer’ of referring back to the Gatsby reference material which does not explain how to fix the problem), I was finally able to see some documentation via the &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt; readme about a potential solution which ended up resolving it for me:  Clearing the cache for &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt; via &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;node_modules/gh-pages/.cache&lt;/code&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passing along this information to folks who may also be looking for a fix. 💜 ✨&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/wisdom_of_the_ancients.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;Wisdom of the Ancients&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moving Over to Gatsby]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is the first post since migrating my personal website from using Middleman to using GatsbyJS + Dimension Starter. 🚀 Doing the…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//moving-over-to-gatsby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//moving-over-to-gatsby/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is the first post since migrating my personal website from using Middleman to using GatsbyJS + Dimension Starter. 🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing the migration was a whole lot more straightforward than I thought it would be. What made the ease of migration possible was mainly due to the existance of modules, starters, and excellent documentation to help with getting started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m very excited to begin my journey in working more actively with the JavaScript ecosystem. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having been rooted in the Ruby community for several years, it’s an interesting change of pace to take a peek into what other communities are doing, what the development patterns are, and how folks interact with eachother.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>