<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[brennx0rblog.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The brennx0r.com blog.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:35:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[🔭  Looking Towards the Next Adventure]]></title><description><![CDATA[After taking a break earlier this year, I am excited to announce that I am officially looking for my next career adventure, interviewing now…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//looking-for-next-adventure/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//looking-for-next-adventure/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;After taking a break earlier this year, I am excited to announce that I am officially looking for my next career adventure, interviewing now with the goal of beginning with a company in early CYQ3 this year (August - September preferred).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For prospective employers, I have put together a reverse job posting, using the approach I’ve seen most recently used by the amazing Julie Pagano (&lt;a href=&quot;https://juliepagano.com/blog/2022/04/21/available-for-work-late-2022/&quot; target=new&gt;hire her!&lt;/a&gt;). I hope this format will prove useful for folks who want to know a little bit more about me than what’s contained within my resume.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#When&quot;&gt;When&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Where&quot;&gt;Where&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#About-Me&quot;&gt;About me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#what-im-looking-for&quot;&gt;What I’m looking for&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#location&quot;&gt;Location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#working-hours&quot;&gt;Working Hours&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#size&quot;&gt;Size&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#type-of-work&quot;&gt;Type of work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#culture&quot;&gt;Culture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#extras&quot;&gt;Extras&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#pros&quot;&gt;Pros&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#cons&quot;&gt;Cons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#deal-breakers&quot;&gt;Deal-breakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#contact-me&quot;&gt;Contact me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#faqs&quot;&gt;FAQs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;When&quot;&gt;⌚️ When&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I am actively engaging in interview discussions beginning &lt;strong&gt;now&lt;/strong&gt;, please be aware that &lt;strong&gt;my preferred earliest start date is Monday, August 1st&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;my latest preferred start date is Monday, October 3rd&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, if your preferred start date for an open role is earlier than this time frame, I am open to the discussion regarding an earlier start date. Let’s chat!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;Where&quot;&gt;🌎 Where&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I live in Seattle, WA. I am exclusively looking to join remote / distributed-first organizations.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I am open to work travel once the COVID-19 pandemic is over, at this current time I will not be open to travel based on the virus transmission levels within the US. That said, I am happy to organize or attend any organizational events remotely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I deeply miss collaborating with colleagues in in-person settings (summits, off-site events, etc.), and I am looking forward to a future where it is safe to return to this type of collaboration.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;About-Me&quot;&gt;👩🏻‍🎤 About Me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for high-level information about my professional experience, please refer to &lt;a href=&quot;/brenna-flood-resume-eba585b180a362f5be6de20af6014d04.pdf&quot;&gt;my resume&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/brennaflood&quot; target=new&gt;LinkedIn profile&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a queer, bilingual (English, Spanish) dual (Bermudian, American) citizen who was half-raised in Bermuda, half-raised in Las Vegas, Nevada. My cultural and personal identity is a fabric based on those truths.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working in the tech industry for over 20 years, beginning with an entry-level support role. I learned and progressed over a landscape of different interests, mastering each and moving towards my passions as I went: Technical Support, Systems Engineering, Software Quality Assurance, Build and Release Engineering, and Production Engineering / SRE. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I have a college education (with educational emphasis in the areas of political science, environmental science, economics), everything I’ve learned about the industry - technologies, processes, and procedures - has all been self-taught: Exploration through reading, attending conferences, hands-on learning, talking to field experts, and attending specific trainings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I enjoy working with others to solve complex problems to make communities better. I am adept at understanding organizations and systems at a macro-level as well as a micro-level, and my managering is a reflection of this understanding. I am highly organized and love building helpful, concise documentation frameworks to help people express ideas and hone engagement and learning. I care about outcomes. I optimize towards learning, reflection, then action: Move deliberately and fix things. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I care very deeply about people, and believe that treating folks with kindness and respect in the workplace should have, at a minimum, equal care and weight as OKRs, KPIs, or other business objectives, as it’s &lt;strong&gt;people&lt;/strong&gt; that complete those business objectives. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/financial-edge/0711/the-cost-of-hiring-a-new-employee.aspx&quot; target=new&gt;Hiring is expensive&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marcusoft.net/2017/09/teams-are-immutable-cooperation-structures.html&quot; target=new&gt;Teams are immutable&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://hbr.org/2017/08/high-performing-teams-need-psychological-safety-heres-how-to-create-it&quot;&gt;Building trust and psychological safety&lt;/a&gt; ultimately builds high-performing, creative teams - vital building blocks to the health of any business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s so much more I would detail, but I’ll leave you with the following potential conversation-starters. I can tell you many tales about wide changes (configuration management, virtualization,emerging technologies, etc.) I’ve seen in the industry over my career, and (probably) why the changes happened. I can tell you all about all the times/ways I’ve broken production, or worked through the pain of multi-hour production deployments, or have reduced cycle time from months to days to hours to minutes, and why those time scales have massive impacts for organizations. I can tell you all about the amazing, smart, incredible people I’ve had the distinct honor and privilege to work with. I can tell you about that one time I made 10+ muppet-style puppets to put on a show with two of my favorite people, sending a love letter to our favorite conference talks for one of my favorite programming languages. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If any of my story and experience is compelling to you, and you’d like to reach out to me, here’s some of the things I am looking for…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;what-im-looking-for&quot;&gt;🔎 What I’m looking for&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my next adventure, I want to be a leader in an organization that cares about and supports:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;👥 &lt;strong&gt;People.&lt;/strong&gt; What is the company strategy and philosophy regarding employee retention and support? What do you value in the interviewing experience? Offer? Pay and Benefits? Career progression and learning? What practices and procedures do you have in support of DEI and healthy cultures? What are the key areas where the company is making investments? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every company has this challenge to get these questions right for the needs of the business. Some companies care and actively reflect on how to evolve and strengthen values surrounding employee care, and others - based on many business reasons - don’t prioritize people. I prefer to be a part of businesses who make big bets on their people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;🧱 &lt;strong&gt;Sustainability&lt;/strong&gt;. Is it clear how decisions are made at the company? If not entirely clear, what discussions, forums, actions are happening to gain better clarity? Is roadmapping discussion unidirectional or bi-directional? What is the company burn rate? What is the runway? LTV? CAC? As a manager, what tools do I have at the ready to engage and collaborate with folks to ensure business objectives are met?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;📜 &lt;strong&gt;Clear, Moral Mission and Values&lt;/strong&gt;. The past few years have been particularly challenging - for businesses, communities, and individuals. With the increased intensity of climate change, societal change, I believe that it’s important - now more than ever - to join an organization with a clear, actionable company mission that results in a net-positive good for communities around the world.  Good examples of what I’m talking about: Direct support of clean technology, providing equity to communities without access, providing technology that makes people happier and healthier (music production, education, information discovery, etc.). Beyond this, what forums or communication loops does the company have to encourage discussion about what moral or ethical implications surrounding the things we are building?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;💰 &lt;strong&gt;Equitable Level and Compensation&lt;/strong&gt;. Commensurate with my level of technical leadership and management experience, level and pay aligned with M2 described in many tech organizations for the Seattle area &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.levels.fyi/comp.html?track=Software%20Engineering%20Manager&amp;search=M2&amp;region=819&amp;yoestart=5&amp;yoeend=10&amp;yoeradio=Senior%20Level&amp;workarrangement=Remote&quot; target=new&gt;(levels.fyi)&lt;/a&gt; is appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;location&quot;&gt;🏙 Location&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t matter much to me where the company HQ is, as long as the People team can support US, Bermuda, &lt;strong&gt;or&lt;/strong&gt; Canada-based employees (taxes, benefits, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;working-hours&quot;&gt;🎹 Working Hours &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My preferred working hours are between 9AM - 5PM Pacific, with room for flexibility to tend to the normal day-to-day things: Have lunch, get exercise, or step away for a walk to reflect so that I can make the best, forward-thinking, creative solutions in support of my colleagues. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;size&quot;&gt;🎚 Size&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My ideal organization size is between &lt;strong&gt;50 and 250 employees, where I am managing 6 - 15 people (managing ICs or managing managers)&lt;/strong&gt;. I am very comfortable managing at this level and will remain happy managing at this level for the forseeable future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this company size doesn’t fit your org, I may still be open to speaking with you about roles if you are in a place where there’s sprawl and complexity, you have identified at an org level that change is needed, and you intend to hire someone with the budget and latitude to make changes happen. I have a proven track record across my career to be able not only evaluate areas of change and conduct audits, but also fulfilling the commitment of making changes happen in support of reduced technical complexity and tool cost reduction (while documenting and standardizing along the way).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/i-love-mess-32e344afd75213be1b8dfea84943f193.gif&quot; alt=&quot;I love mess.&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;type-of-work&quot;&gt;🧩 Type of Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am interested in managing a SDET, QA, CI/CD, Infra, Release, Platform, or DevOps team/organization. I’ve managed single teams (4-6 FTE) and I have also managed multiple teams with entirely different functions simultaneously (4-6 FTE; 2-3 contractors). While I feel comfortable with managering at both scopes, when starting at any company I’d prefer managing a single team before segueing to managing multiple teams, in order to ensure I have time to learn as much as I can about the company, setup, people, etc. before branching out in management responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;culture&quot;&gt;💞 Culture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People&lt;/strong&gt;: Smart, Kind, Growth Mindset, and open to change, empathetic, and inclusive. Prefers data-driven decisions and changes.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote work &amp;#x26; flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;: Teams have the tools they need to collaborate effectively without being in the same room. People are comfortable with asynchronous communication to account for teammates with varying schedules and time zones. Meetings are used thoughtfully and sparingly to ensure people have focus time to complete heads down work like coding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication and Feedback&lt;/strong&gt;: Folks in the organization embrace true bi-directional feedback across the business. No matter who or where you are in the organization - from IC to C-level leadership: A genuine interest in getting candid, kind feedback. Folks believe that receiving constructive, actionable feedback is a gift.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;: Folks work together as a team to solve problems. Work is not done on islands or in secret. &lt;a href=&quot;https://hbr.org/2021/03/does-your-company-lurch-from-crisis-to-crisis&quot; target=new&gt;Prefers “No Hero” culture&lt;/a&gt;. People err on the side of writing things down to share information with others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work/Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: You prefer to work smart at a sustainable pace, so you are successful with a low risk of burnout. People work about ~40 hours a week or less and accomplish a lot because of focus and alignment. Working on nights or weekends only happens rarely in extreme situations. When people leave work at the end of the day or go on vacation, they are able to disconnect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Celebration&lt;/strong&gt;: The company makes space for celebrating teams for their work and reaching key milestones - not only through shoutouts, but through team events as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;extras&quot;&gt;👑 Extras&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It would be amazing to speak with companies who have the following policies in place:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.4dayweek.com/&quot;&gt;Standardized 4-day work week&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/worklife/article/20220426-could-menstrual-leave-change-the-workplace&quot; target=new&gt;Menstrual Leave&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hrdive.com/news/paid-time-off-doesnt-work-but-minimum-time-off-does/602674/&quot; target=new&gt;Minimum PTO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;pros&quot;&gt;👍🏻 Pros&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am looking for the following benefits in my next company:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your company has a great mission and values framework. Bonus points to work involving environmental science, education, indie gaming, art, or music.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A flexible working schedule&lt;/strong&gt;. As mentioned earlier, I tend to work between 9AM - 5PM Pacific. While I can start/end later in the day by a few hours, I am not available earlier than 9AM.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At least 3 weeks paid vacation&lt;/strong&gt;. If there is an unlimited PTO policy, I want to know more about what mechanisms are in place company-culture wise to ensure that folks are getting enough time off to rest and recharge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unlimited sick leave&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;401K match&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health benefits are mostly or 100% paid for by the company, and includes vision and dental coverage&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mental health care is included in health care coverage, and is not a 3rd party service offering like Ginger&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional time off in support of learning, conferences, outreach, and volunteerism.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;cons&quot;&gt;👎🏻 Cons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have recently had or expect to have an executive leadership change.&lt;/strong&gt; While I’m still open to discussing roles, I will want to take additional time in discussion to understand why the change is happening, as well as what the strategy pivots the business will have to make to responsibly adapt (hiring the new leader and what the interview process is like, evaluating in-flight projects, staffing, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role has little to no functional or fiscal agency to direct and manage positive team or organizational change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Existing policies and procedures in the company are inflexible, or company is not open to change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On-call expectation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employee support/DEI:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The DEI head reports to HR/People team&lt;/strong&gt;. I’ll want to have a conversation with you about how you manage to separate potential conflicts of interest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Affinity groups are expected to be led by employees with no additional compensation or acknowledgement of the additional time commitment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security team&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team is fewer than 3 people and/or security consulting is not actively engaged for systems audits and remediation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Actively contributes to political causes.&lt;/strong&gt; I’ll want to have a conversation with you about where the company donates (GOP? Democrat? ACLU? etc.) within any given year, with the reasons why.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;deal-breakers&quot;&gt;🚫 Deal-breakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below are company deal-breakers - your company goals/interests/policies and mine are not aligned:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type of company/work&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your company is Google, Meta, Amazon, Microsoft, Starbucks, Palantir&lt;/strong&gt;. Additionally, if your company engages in any of the following, I am not interested in working for you:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggregation and use of PII data with the goal of influencing, marketing, or otherwise manipulating people without their knowledge or consent (ala Cambridge Analytica);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gig work;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Associated with weapons, arms, defense, police. Additionally, any collaboration with private or governmental institutions (Eg. DOD, DHS, ICE, CIA, FBI; Lockheed-Martin, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anything involving blockchain, crypto, NFTs, web3, etc.;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively engaged in union-busting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interviewing Expectations&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inclusion of any coding exercise - take home or otherwise&lt;/strong&gt;. I am interviewing for a management role, not an IC role. If you want to get an idea of my understanding of programming, please refer to my &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r&quot; target=new&gt;Github profile and project repos&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-hour take home exercise&lt;/strong&gt;. I will be interviewing with many companies, and I don’t have the time to engage in that scope of time investment.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expectation to work in an office in a part-time or full-time capacity;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel (during the pandemic)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Culture and Dynamics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expects off-hours communication;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any sector of employees within the company are not given a living wage or inclusive hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employee support/DEI:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You don’t have an HR team.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You don’t have a recruiting team.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You cannot disclose employee demographic information when requested by me or anyone else within a reasonable amount of time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You don’t have any women/non-binary folks in engineering leadership.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineering management roles where the working expectation is to manage and also directly make code contributions to projects.&lt;/strong&gt; I personally don’t believe that great management for a team can happen where the manager is also directly contributing. In addition to issues relating to contributions and power dynamics, I think the decreased focus on people management will result in negative outcomes for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;contact-me&quot;&gt;☎️ Contact me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If what I’ve written resonates with you and you’d like to speak with me about roles at your company, &lt;a href=&quot;https://calendly.com/brennaflood&quot; target=new&gt;please book time with me to chat&lt;/a&gt;! So that I’m prepared for the conversation, please include a little bit about yourself, the role/req, and a little bit about the company. Looking forward to speaking with you. 💜 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id=&quot;faqs&quot;&gt;FAQs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you open to IC roles?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not at this time.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Setting up Nintendo Switch with Elgato HD60S For Twitch Streaming]]></title><description><![CDATA[While I’ve been on sabbatical, I’ve used the time to revisit and tackle projects that I’ve been putting off for one reason or another. One…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//Switch_Elgato_Twitch_Setup/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//Switch_Elgato_Twitch_Setup/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;While I’ve been on sabbatical, I’ve used the time to revisit and tackle projects that I’ve been putting off for one reason or another. One project in that list has been to set up my Switch to Stream to Twitch using my home office desk workstation setup so that I can chat with the online community and share my Animal Crossing: New Horizons Island, based on places in Bermuda - including St. David’s, Fort St. Catherine, Cupmatch pitch and fan site, the Hamilton Princess spa, and more! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After spending a few hours looking at software options, testing them out for my needs, I ran into some traps and hazards before finally getting everything settled. With that in mind, I thought it would be useful to share the setup experience with y’all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;My Use Case and Desired Outcomes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MVP:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch content shared to Twitch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gameplay sound and commentary sound available to Twitch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Locally, be able to listen to the video game music AND be able to provide commentary simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customizable transition screens to make the Twitch experience more professional&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sharing profile video on the stream&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Custom stats, new subs, other metadata on the stream&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Hardware&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Nintendo Switch with dock (dock is required to access HDMI output)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An A/V capture device (this tutorial will focus specifically on the Elgato HD60S)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a MacBook Pro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Cabling&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One USBC cable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One HDMI cable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;… and finally: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Software&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A software studio solution that you can use to display the captured video and audio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, I will go over 2 options: &lt;strong&gt;OBS and Elgato Game Capture HD&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please keep in mind that this doesn’t cover the full range of what’s out there, and like all tech tutorials, the value of this information is going to degrade over time as new versions of software become available and compatibilty, experiences change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hardware / Cabling Setup&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is a rough outline of what that looks like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;../switch_elgato_computer_hardware_setup.png&quot; alt=&quot;Hardware Setup Topology&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;OBS Setup Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First off, I wanted to download and install the latest version of OBS. At the time of this blog post, that version is v 27.2.4 (3/29/22). Once this version is installed, there are some other software dependencies that you must install before OBS will work properly:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OBS Link (&lt;a href=&quot;https://help.elgato.com/hc/en-us/articles/360031363132-OBS-Link-Setup&quot;&gt;https://help.elgato.com/hc/en-us/articles/360031363132-OBS-Link-Setup&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BIG NOTES ON FUNCTIONALITY:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OBS Link is not compatible with Apple Silicon Macs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;OBS Link has a latency around ~250ms. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the latency might not seem like a big deal for some games (Animal Crossing or other chill puzzle games), for others (like sidescrollers, action, etc.) it means that the “feel” in response time made the games nearly unplayable. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried hacking at the latency for better performance, and while there is a mode for the NDI input in OBS for “better performance” I’ve found it only works for about 30 seconds, then the latency increases, followed by the game sound crashing and cutting out. The only way to resolve that behavior was to entirely quit and restart OBS. In short, a very poor experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Elgato Software Setup Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over on the Elgato-native software side, I installed Elgato Game Capture HD v2.11.14 (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.elgato.com/en/game-capture-software&quot;&gt;https://www.elgato.com/en/game-capture-software&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After installation, I found that it was pretty straight-forward to set up the elgato device, the sound setup, the microphone setup, as well as the set up of some custom transitions screens. The only issue I came across that I have yet to resolve is that I cannot play game sound locally when I have “Commentary” turned on - even if I want to pipe out the game audio via headphones. I should also note here that the audience experience is that they will hear both. I reckon that this is a feature of the software to avoid echo or looping issues in sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an upcoming blog post, I’ll delve a little deeper into the UI/UX of this application, as well as setting up the transitions screens, setting up gaming stats from Twitch, and more - stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;🌯 In Conclusion…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was very pleasantly surprised by the experience in picking up and using Game Capture HD vs. OBS. While I have been an OBS user in the past, the recent software changes that required OBS Link to be installed cut the usability and functionality I need for my use cases. While I will continue to use OBS for other purposes, I recommend that if folks have the Elgato HD60S that they use Game Capture HD instead as it’s easier to use and set up, doesn’t have latency issues, and simply has better performance.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Planning Our Recent 2019 UK Trip! 🚀 💂‍♀️]]></title><description><![CDATA[As you may have seen from recent tweets, Jer and I recently took a trip to the UK. Specifically, London, then Scotland, then back to London…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//2019_uk_trip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//2019_uk_trip/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;As you may have seen from recent tweets, Jer and I recently took a trip to the UK. Specifically, London, then Scotland, then back to London. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea for the trip was kicked off when reflecting upon going to Maui for my birthday last year. It was an incredible experience, and I wanted to be able to reciprocate for Jer by taking him to the top locations on his “bucket list.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Various folks on Twitter have requested that I create a blog post that discusses the process I use to plan a trip. I hope you find the below information useful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;So now that there’s a location in mind, how the heck to begin planning? 🤔&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;🗣 Collaboration Tools Make It Happen!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are planning a trip with anyone, you’re gonna need a collaboration tool which you can collectively reference what needs to be planned, what’s already been considered and booked, as well as a common reference place for information - hotel names and addresses, booking reference numbers, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These tools can look anything like the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keybase&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google Drive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git(hu|la)b&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these can be fine choices, but the important bit is that everyone involved in the planning should enjoy using the tool, and the tool should have some security-mindedness (ACLs, etc.) so that if you opt to include sensitive information, this information is kept safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below I’ll go through the detail concerning all the bits and bobs I find to be handy in this common collaboration space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;📅 Timeline of Events&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Jer and me, doing touristy stuff doesn’t rank highly on the list (if at all), so we don’t need to manage every hour of the day with markers of all those little events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, it still makes sense when planning a trip (especially one with multiple locations involved) to have a timeline of events within easy reach. Even if you think you are planning a “simple trip”, having a timeline will help tease all sorts of shapes/sizes of logistics to you haven’t immediately considered concerning the timings between the transportation, flights, hotel, meals. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, you may realize that by booking an early morning flight that you have consequently cheated yourself out of a decent breakfast at the hotel and will consequently either need to seek out food at the airport or schedule a later flight. Or, you may find that by arriving late in the evening, unless you call the hotel and schedule a late check-in ahead of time, no one will be available to give you a room key. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going through this exercise will take a bit of time up-front, this will ultimately &lt;em&gt;save&lt;/em&gt; you time, anxiety, and headache of having to deal with the fallout of a poorly considered timing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#timeline&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Markdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  In our recent trip, Jer used emoji markers with a legend for various things and it was &lt;strong&gt;DELIGHTFUL&lt;/strong&gt;. 💜&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/open?id=1UEENlY462nlyEfyC-sGdklDfSEOFOfqFC5q_itmI-_4&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Drive Spreadsheet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared Calendars&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://support.apple.com/kb/ph2690?locale=en_US&quot;&gt;Apple&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://support.google.com/calendar/answer/37082?hl=en&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;📋 To-Do List&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It seems obvious, but mentioning here regardless! I live by to-do lists. In a collaborative setting, doubly so because it makes sure that everyone is on the same page at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, in seeing and making use of the list, it may prompt the brain to think of other things that should be added to the list. For example, in the last trip after ‘completing’ the To-Do list, I noticed that we hadn’t considered a taxi from a train station to a very remote hotel in the evening. 😅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#bookingsreservations-status&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;🗝📕 ‘What’s Booked’ Metadata&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This can be flight, car, train, hotel, and all sorts of other reference information. A few pointers before adding the information:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you really need the sensitive information in the collaboration tool?&lt;/strong&gt; Some providers don’t really need this information anymore, and you can communicate with them directly via mobile apps instead of having to keep track of reference or booking numbers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make sure that the collaboration tool is secure&lt;/strong&gt;, where only contributors involved in the trip can reference the information. Do your research to see if the tool is secure enough for your purposes. Not sure? Don’t store your information in the tool. ✨&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#flight-information&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;💡 Open Dreams / Questions / Logistics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Daydreaming about the possibilities during a trip is lovely, so why not share those thoughts so that the ideas aren’t lost? I’ve found that even when we find we don’t have time on &lt;em&gt;this trip&lt;/em&gt; for a dream, that we can save that idea for a later voyage. Sharing dreams brings joy. 🌈&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Examples&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/brennx0r/trip_planning_template/blob/master/trip_template.MD#-ideas--wouldnt-it-be-neat-if&quot;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;🌯 In Conclusion…&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that these templates, pointers, and examples helped to spark new ideas about your upcoming adventures. If there’s a section which you’d like more information, or if you’d like to engage with me on related topics, please feel free to DM me on Twitter (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/brennx0r&quot;&gt;@brennx0r&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers! &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bullet-Journaling]]></title><description><![CDATA[A couple months ago I purchased a Cricut Explore Air 2 following the binge watch of YouTube videos showcasing comparisons between various…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//bullet-journaling/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//bullet-journaling/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A couple months ago I purchased a Cricut Explore Air 2 following the binge watch of YouTube videos showcasing comparisons between various models. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ch23OY8z5Fo&quot;&gt;This video&lt;/a&gt; was great in doing various tests (cut precision, speed test, sound test) between the machines, which led me to buy the Cricut!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, I decided to unbox it and do a couple of basic projects to better understand the features. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Verdict:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; It’s an awesome little machine and I’m looking forward to using it for all sorts of different projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first big project? Bullet Journaling template stickers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now I’m putting together the scaffold of a YouTube video on the subject of effective bullet journaling, which will lead into a quick how-to on creating templates for quickly putting together a new book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Scaffold&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;- What is/Why Bullet Journaling?
- General Starting Layout
  - Intro 
- Modifying the &amp;#39;Default&amp;#39; Layout
- Bullet Journaling as Agile
- Demo / Process
  - Starting point: Chronological notebook (not using bullet journaling, per say)
  - Iteration: Noticing Patterns, Grouping What&amp;#39;s Important
  - Create the Bullet Journal
    - Draw out the format 
    - Create Template Stickers
    - Move boldly forward&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that y’all enjoy it once it’s posted.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[botd]]></title><description><![CDATA[In a Twitter conversation between a couple friends, the topic of 
“Which Belcher are you?” came up. And clearly, I am Bob. Clearly. This has…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//botd/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//botd/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;In a Twitter conversation between a couple friends, the topic of
“Which Belcher are you?” came up. And clearly, I am Bob. Clearly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has led to one of the friends in the conversation - @sweetpavement - to
begin to prompt me for a Burger of the Day (BOTD) each weekday as a tweet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since this has been going on for longer than a week, I’m finding that an archive
list is now needed to make sure that I’m not repeating puns, and to showcase
this sacriliciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;BOTD&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When I Dip, You Dip, We Dip! Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Burger with Swiss and onions on a traditional baguette with jus on the side)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/12/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Pleased to Meat You Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (3 quarter pound patties - beef, pork, and chorizo - with caramelized onions layered between)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/11/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curry On My Wayward Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Panko-ed patty topped with traditional Japanese curry)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/10/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I Am a Super Fungi Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Filled with buttery chanterelle and lobster mushrooms and a kiss of swiss cheese)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/7/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We Make a Great Pear Burger!&lt;/strong&gt; (Super thin slices of pear, crispy applewood smoked bacon)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/6/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kind of a big dill burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Tzatziki sauce, extra dill, thin sliced tomatoes and cucumbers)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/5/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The I Do Not Want To Taco Bout It Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Seasoned patty w/ additional taco meat on top, sharp cheddar, tomato, lettuce, sour cream, and salty tears)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;12/3/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nacho ordinary burger!&lt;/strong&gt; (Thin tortilla strips w/ gourmet queso)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11/30/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Make Miso Happy Burger&lt;/strong&gt; (Hugged by a lattice of bacon and kissed with micro greens)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11/29/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Goudas around comes around burger&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;11/28/2018&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Updating website; Woes Ensue!]]></title><description><![CDATA[After not updating my site for a couple of months, I was looking to update with a new blog post. As it turns out, I had forgotten the setup…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//updating-site-woes-ensue/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//updating-site-woes-ensue/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;After not updating my site for a couple of months, I was looking to update with a new blog post. As it turns out, I had forgotten the setup/layout for the Gatsby starter I was using, so updating it was very difficult. I ended up scrapping the whole thing for another starter template which is much simpler, easier to read and extend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other woes I ran into had to deal with the npm module &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt;, caching and deployment. In trying to deploy to repo &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;brennx0r.github.io&lt;/code&gt;, master branch - I kept getting this error:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;bash
fatal: A branch named ‘master’ already exists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;npm ERR! code ELIFECYCLE
npm ERR! errno 1
npm ERR! gatsby-starter-blog@1.0.0 deploy: &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gatsby build &amp;amp;&amp;amp; gh-pages -d public -b &amp;gt; master -r git@github.com:brennx0r/brennx0r.github.io.git&lt;/code&gt;
npm ERR! Exit status 1
npm ERR! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After scouring a number of sites (and frustratingly getting the ‘answer’ of referring back to the Gatsby reference material which does not explain how to fix the problem), I was finally able to see some documentation via the &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt; readme about a potential solution which ended up resolving it for me:  Clearing the cache for &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gh-pages&lt;/code&gt; via &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;node_modules/gh-pages/.cache&lt;/code&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Passing along this information to folks who may also be looking for a fix. 💜 ✨&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/wisdom_of_the_ancients.png&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot; title=&quot;Wisdom of the Ancients&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Moving Over to Gatsby]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is the first post since migrating my personal website from using Middleman to using GatsbyJS + Dimension Starter. 🚀 Doing the…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//moving-over-to-gatsby/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-blog-demo.netlify.com//moving-over-to-gatsby/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is the first post since migrating my personal website from using Middleman to using GatsbyJS + Dimension Starter. 🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing the migration was a whole lot more straightforward than I thought it would be. What made the ease of migration possible was mainly due to the existance of modules, starters, and excellent documentation to help with getting started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m very excited to begin my journey in working more actively with the JavaScript ecosystem. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having been rooted in the Ruby community for several years, it’s an interesting change of pace to take a peek into what other communities are doing, what the development patterns are, and how folks interact with eachother.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>